A Guide to the Thomas N. Downing Papers, 1947-1977
Library of Virginia
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 551)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - News Releases (4 folders)
    - News Contacts, n.d.
    - Publications and Photographs (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 552)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity.
    - Publications and Photographs (1 folder)
    - Photographs, 1976
  - Political Files.
    - Accomack County
    - Bentsen for President
    - Campaign, 1976
    - Campaign Contributions
    - Democratic National Committee
    - Democratic [Party]
    - Dean of Virginia Delegation
    - Downing Retirement--General and Correspondence (2 folders).
      Note: The Retirement Letters folders contain a package of open-reel magnetic tape; it is a print of an interview with Downing by WVEC, Hampton.
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 553)
  - Political Files.
    - Retirement Letters (2 folders)
    - Federal Election Campaign Laws (2 folders)
    - State Election Campaign Laws (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 554)
  - Political Files.
    - Expenses, 1974 Campaign
    - First District
    - First District Congressional Seat
    - Newport News, City of
    - Northern Neck
    - Presidential Candidates, 1976
    - Quinn, Robert
    - Report of Receipts and Expenditures--Candidate
    - Report of Receipts and Expenditures--District Fund
    - Political Supplies
    - Commonwealth of Virginia
    - State Democratic Election--Finances
    - Westmoreland County
    - York County
  - Speech Files.
    - Chronological Files, January-February 1975 (2 folders)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 555)
  - Speech Files.
    - Chronological Files, January-December 1976 (3 folders)
    - Commencement Speeches
    - Speeches on Congress--Duties, etc.
    - Historical Speeches
    - Merchant Marine Speeches
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 556)
  - Speech Files.
    - Patriotic Speeches
    - Speech Materials (2 folders)
    - Extension of Remarks, 1975-1976 (2 folders)
  - Voting Record.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (1 folder)
- 94th Congress, 1975-1976. (Box 557)
  - Voting Record.
    - 1st and 2nd Sessions (1 volume)
- Speech Files, Undated and No Congress Specified. (Box 557)
  - General Topic Speeches (4 folders)
  - Agriculture Speeches
- Speech Files, Undated and No Congress Specified. (Box 558)
  - Appropriations Speeches (2 folders)
  - Armed Services Speeches (2 folders)
  - Foreign Affairs Speeches (2 folders)
  - Government Operations Speeches
  - Interior and Insular Affairs Speeches
- Speech Files, Undated and No Congress Specified. (Box 559)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Speeches (2 folders)
  - Judiciary Committee Speeches (2 folders)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Speeches and Materials (4 folders)
- Speech Files, Undated and No Congress Specified. (Box 560)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Speeches (5 folders)
  - Political Speeches (2 folders)
- Speech Files, Undated and No Congress Specified. (Box 561)
  - Political Speeches (1 folder)
  - Post Office and Civil Service Speeches (2 folders)
  - Public Works Speeches
  - Religious Speeches
  - Science and Astronautics Speeches (3 folders)
- Speech Files, Undated and No Congress Specified. (Box 562)
  - Science and Astronautics Speeches (3 folders)
  - Select Committee on Small Business Speeches
  - Un-American Activities Committee Speeches
  - Veterans Affairs Speeches
  - Ways and Means Speeches (2 folders)